        const scenarios = {
            "1": {
                title: "Principle 1: The charity serves its mission and achieves its objectives.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "A corporate donor offers your {charityType} a $500k restricted grant, but stipulations require diverting 40% of funds to launch an unrelated youth mentorship program. The management team is eager to accept, but it fundamentally distracts from your core mission.", gec: "CODE ID 1.1: Clearly state the charitable purposes (for example, vision and mission, objectives, use of resources, activities, and so on) and include the objectives in the charity's governing instrument. Publish the stated charitable purposes on platforms (for example, Charity Portal, website, social media channels, and so on) that can be easily accessed by the public.", bestPractice: "Strict alignment of funding to the charity's documented core mission and constitutional objectives." },
                    { scenario: "A prominent board member proposes changing your {charityType} main focus to jump on a new trending social cause that attracts easy funding, effectively abandoning your legacy beneficiaries.", gec: "CODE ID 1.2: Develop and implement strategic plans to achieve the stated charitable purposes.", bestPractice: "Strategic planning and continuous evaluation of programs against the charity's defined purpose." },
                    { scenario: "The Executive Director of your {charityType} has quietly started expanding operations overseas without board approval, arguing that the local mission is 'already fulfilled'.", gec: "CODE ID 1.3: Have the Board review the charity's strategic plans regularly to ensure that the charity is achieving its charitable purposes, and monitor, evaluate and report the outcome and impact of its activities.", bestPractice: "Board oversight, authorisation, and approval for significant strategic shifts or geographical expansions." },
                    { scenario: "A major shift in government policy renders your {charityType} main program less effective, yet the management refuses to evaluate new ways of operating because 'this is how we have always done it'.", gec: "CODE ID 1.3: Regularly review strategic plans; monitor, evaluate, and report outcome and impact.", bestPractice: "Regular review of program relevance, impact, and alignment with current community needs." }
                ]
            },
            "2": {
                title: "Principle 2: The charity has an effective Board and Management.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "A charity'€™s Board size falls below the minimum requirement of three members due to unforeseen resignations, impacting the quorum for decision-making.", gec: "CODE ID 2.1: Board Size/Composition", bestPractice: "The Board immediately refers to its search and nomination process to recruit qualified members, ensuring the governing instrument's minimum requirements are met promptly." },
                    { scenario: "The Board Chair of your {charityType} has served for 12 years and firmly resists stepping down, citing a 'lack of ready successors'. Key independent directors are frustrated and threatening to resign over the stagnant leadership.", gec: "CODE ID 2.2: Board Term Limits", bestPractice: "Implementing board renewal policies, succession planning, and strict term limits for independent directors." },
                    { scenario: "A Board member is also a director of a vendor firm that has submitted a highly competitive bid for the charity'€™s IT infrastructure project.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Conflict of Interest", bestPractice: "The member declares the interest in writing and recuses themselves from the evaluation. The Board documents the 'Interested Person Transaction' and the basis for the final vendor selection." },
                    { scenario: "It is discovered that three of the eight board members of your {charityType} have missed over 50% of meetings in the last two years, yet the Chair refuses to ask them to step down because they are 'well connected'.", gec: "CODE ID 5.6: Implement clear reporting structures, maintain meeting minutes, and ensure a quorum of at least half the Board.", bestPractice: "Enforcing minimum attendance requirements and quorum rules for board effectiveness." },
                    { scenario: "The board of your {charityType} consists entirely of close friends of the founder, lacking crucial skills in finance, legal, and digital strategy. They govern primarily by rubber-stamping the founder's decisions.", gec: "CODE ID 2.4: Ensure Board is diverse, appropriately sized, and has a good mix of skills; members must exercise independent judgement.", bestPractice: "Board diversity and competency matrix to ensure a broad mix of independent professional skills." },
                    { scenario: "The Chairman of your {charityType} also actively serves as the Executive Director and CEO, granting them total control without any independent checks.", gec: "CODE ID 2.1: Board and Management roles/responsibilities must be clear and distinct.", bestPractice: "Segregation of duties and clear role division between the Board leadership (Chairman) and Executive management (CEO)." },
                    { scenario: "When a new director is appointed to your {charityType}, there is no formal letter of appointment or onboarding document explaining their fiduciary duties, leaving them confused about their operational role.", gec: "CODE ID 2.2: Board and Management must be inducted and undergo training where necessary.", bestPractice: "Formal onboarding, induction training, and clear letters of appointment for all new directors." },
                    { scenario: "During the annual general meeting, it is noted that the Board has never conducted any form of self-evaluation or performance review for its members over the past five years.", gec: "CODE ID 2.7: Board members must have suitable qualifications, understand their duties, and perform well.", bestPractice: "Periodic board performance evaluation and self-assessment to identify governance gaps." },
                    { scenario: "A board committee takes it upon itself to approve a massive IT overhaul contract without referring back to the main Board, bypassing standard corporate governance protocols.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Board approves the annual budget and reviews internal controls (covering delegation of authority).", bestPractice: "Clear delegation of authority limits, approval matrices, and final board authorisation for major contracts." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} operates without a clear set of documented terms of reference for any of its sub-committees, causing overlapping decisions on finance and HR.", gec: "CODE ID 2.3: Document terms of reference for the Board and committees (Audit and Finance are mandatory).", bestPractice: "Documented Terms of Reference (TOR) defining the scope, authority, and composition of all committees." },
                    { scenario: "There is no formal succession plan established for the aging leadership of your {charityType}, posing a massive operational risk should the CEO retire abruptly.", gec: "CODE ID 2.9: Establish term limits for all Board members (max 10 consecutive years; 2-year break before re-appointment).", bestPractice: "Proactive succession planning and talent management for key leadership and management roles." },
                    { scenario: "The staff turnover is incredibly high, yet the Board considers HR management strictly an 'operational' issue and refuses to review the management's deeply flawed employee retention strategy.", gec: "CODE ID 2.8: Management must have suitable qualifications and perform well; staff members should not vote on Board decisions.", bestPractice: "Board oversight of human resource strategies, performance evaluation, and fair compensation policies." },
                    { scenario: "The Executive Director of your {charityType} awarded a lucrative contract to a vendor firm owned by his brother-in-law without a tender. Although the price was competitive, no conflict of interest was officially declared.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Conflict of Interest", bestPractice: "Formal declaration of conflicts of interest and recusal from related decision-making and approval processes." },
                    { scenario: "A board member of your {charityType} silently votes to approve a massive office relocation, failing to disclose they own the new building being leased.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Conflict of Interest", bestPractice: "Strict conflict of interest policies regarding related-party transactions, disclosures, and board voting permissions." }
                ]
            },
            "3": {
                title: "Principle 3: The charity acts responsibly, fairly and with integrity.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} accepts a huge anonymous donation from a shell company discovered to be linked to a controversial industry that fundamentally conflicts with the charity's values.", gec: "CODE ID 3.3a: Ensure no person in a position to influence the charity's decisions derives any unfair or improper advantage (Board remuneration and restrictions).", bestPractice: "Rigorous donor due diligence, background authentication, and vetting to prevent improper influence or reputational damage." },
                    { scenario: "A newly hired staff member quietly leverages charity resources for a side business, claiming there's no clear rule against it.", gec: "CODE ID 3.3b: Ensure no person in a position to influence the charity's decisions derives any unfair or improper advantage (Staff remuneration and restrictions).", bestPractice: "Establishing clear boundaries for staff remuneration and acceptable boundaries for the usage of charity resources." },
                    { scenario: "A staff member is found using charity funds to host private dinners for their family, but the Board writes it off as a simple 'accounting error'.", gec: "CODE ID 3.4: Establish and apply a Code of Conduct reflecting the charity's values and ethics.", bestPractice: "Establishing and enforcing a clear Code of Conduct for staff regarding ethical behavior and fund usage." },
                    { scenario: "The management team ignores recent severe flooding impacts in the beneficiaries' neighborhoods, arguing environmental concerns are not 'our department'.", gec: "CODE ID 3.5: Take into consideration the ESG factors (Environmental, Social, and Governance) when conducting the charity's activities.", bestPractice: "Integrating ESG framework considerations, risk assessments, and sustainability into daily charitable activities and core planning." },
                    { scenario: "A significant error in the past year's charity tax returns goes entirely unreported because there is no procedure for raising compliance matters to the regulators or the board.", gec: "CODE ID 4.4: Set and review specific internal policies (Legal Compliance).", bestPractice: "Robust regulatory compliance monitoring, periodic audits, and formal reporting frameworks." }
                ]
            },
            "4": {
                title: "Principle 4: The charity is well-managed and plans for the future.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "A donor provides a large restricted grant for 'Digital Literacy' for seniors, but the general fund is currently low on cash for staff salaries.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Board approves the annual budget and reviews internal controls.", bestPractice: "The charity maintains separate fund accounting; restricted funds are utilized strictly for the donor's intent, and inter-fund transfers are only done with explicit Board approval and documentation." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} runs entirely on yearly government grants and currently maintains zero financial reserves. A sudden policy change delays the next grant disbursement by 6 months, leaving the charity unable to make payroll next week.", gec: "CODE ID 4.6: Measure impact and respond to risks for long-term sustainability (Reserves Management).", bestPractice: "Documented reserves policy establishing and maintaining adequate operating reserves to ensure financial sustainability whilst monitoring specific expenditures." },
                    { scenario: "The finance manager of your {charityType} has been single-handedly approving all expenses without dual signatories for two years, and an internal audit reveals $50,000 in 'unexplained' miscellaneous spending.", gec: "CODE ID 4.1: Board approves the annual budget and reviews internal controls.", bestPractice: "Segregation of duties, dual authorisations, and multi-level approval matrices for all financial transactions." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} decides to invest 80% of its cash reserves into a high-risk crypto-currency fund, promising double-digit returns to quickly solve a funding deficit.", gec: "CODE ID 4.2: Board approval required for loans, donations, or financial assistance provided by the charity outside of core programs.", bestPractice: "Establishing approved investment policies with defined risk tolerance levels, allowable asset classes, and required board authorisation." },
                    { scenario: "The charity consistently runs enormous multi-year operational deficits but has no formal plan to restore its financial health beyond hoping for a sudden influx of public donations.", gec: "CODE ID 4.6: Measure impact and respond to risks for long-term sustainability (Strategic Financial Planning).", bestPractice: "Aligning financial planning and budget forecasting with long-term strategic plans and available resources." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} signs a complex and extremely expensive 10-year IT software license, but no comprehensive risk assessment or budget analysis was presented to the Board.", gec: "CODE ID 4.3: Implement a risk management system to identify and manage key risks.", bestPractice: "Enterprise risk management processes, comprehensive risk assessments, and executive approval prior to major commitments." },
                    { scenario: "An aging IT system crashes for two days, and it is discovered the charity has zero data backup facilities or any documented business continuity plan.", gec: "CODE ID 4.5: Audit Committee/Board must ensure effectiveness of operational policies and IT processes.", bestPractice: "Implementing, documenting, and periodically testing robust Business Continuity Plans (BCP) and Disaster Recovery (DR) protocols." },
                    { scenario: "Third-party fundraiser agents contracted by your charity are misleading donors on the streets with aggressive hard-sell tactics that clearly violate the sector's ethical guidelines.", gec: "CODE ID 4.4: Set and review specific internal policies (Fundraising).", bestPractice: "Ethical fundraising guidelines, transparent donor communications, and strict oversight and authorisation of third-party agents." }
                ]
            },
            "5": {
                title: "Principle 5: The charity is accountable and transparent.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "A server containing sensitive personal data of 2,000 donors to your {charityType} was inadvertently exposed online. The Executive Director suggests quietly patching it without notifying the Board or Authorities to avoid jeopardizing a major fundraising campaign.", gec: "CODE ID 4.4: Set and review specific internal policies (Data Protection).", bestPractice: "Strict data privacy protocols, secure system authentication, compliance with PDPA, and immediate breach reporting requirements." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} quietly decides to not publish its annual report or financial statements online, claiming 'administrative burden', leading to public speculation about mismanagement of public donations.", gec: "CODE ID 5.1: The charity makes available to its stakeholders an annual report on its programmes, activities, and finances. Comply with the Charity Transparency Framework. (First batch due by June 2025 for FY ending Dec 2024).", bestPractice: "Commitment to public transparency by publishing comprehensive annual reports and audited financial statements under the new framework." },
                    { scenario: "Whistleblowers within your {charityType} formally report severe workplace harassment to the board, but the HR committee buries the report entirely to protect a 'star' fundraising executive.", gec: "CODE ID 5.7: Implement and maintain a whistle-blowing policy.", bestPractice: "Establishing an independent, confidential, and protected whistle-blowing channel overseen directly by the board." },
                    { scenario: "A major international donor explicitly demands detailed reporting on exactly how their restricted grant was spent, but the finance department lacks project-based accounting to trace the exact expenses.", gec: "CODE ID 5.1: Timely and accurate submission of annual reports and financial statements to regulators (Restricted Funds).", bestPractice: "Restricted fund accounting logic, precise tracking of donor-designated funds, and timely accountability reporting to stakeholders." },
                    { scenario: "There is no formal external audit of the charity's financial records despite its income significantly exceeding the legal threshold that mandates one.", gec: "CODE ID 5.1: Timely and accurate submission of annual reports and financial statements to regulators.", bestPractice: "Timely appointment of independent external auditors to authenticate financial integrity and regulatory compliance." },
                    { scenario: "The board members regularly use their charity email to conduct personal business, bringing the charity into potentially awkward liability issues without a clear IT usage policy.", gec: "CODE ID 4.5: Audit Committee/Board must ensure effectiveness of operational policies and IT processes (Accountability).", bestPractice: "Acceptable use policies, secure authentication, and accountability frameworks for utilizing organizational IT resources." },
                    { scenario: "A large number of volunteers are operating high-risk machinery at a charity event without adequate safety briefings or liability waivers because 'they are just helping out'.", gec: "CODE ID 4.4: Set and review specific internal policies (Volunteer Management).", bestPractice: "Comprehensive volunteer management policies, documented safety training, risk mitigation procedures, and liability documentation." },
                    { scenario: "Top executives are receiving excessively lavish salaries that total over 60% of the entire charity'€™s operational budget, yet these figures are intentionally hidden from the public.", gec: "CODE ID 5.4: Disclose remuneration of the top three staff exceeding $100k.", bestPractice: "Full transparency and public disclosure of key management personnel remuneration and compensation structures." }
                ]
            },
            "6": {
                title: "Principle 6: The charity communicates actively to instil public confidence.",
                pool: [
                    { scenario: "During a public appeal, the charity receives feedback that its third-party fundraisers are using high-pressure tactics that contradict the charity's values.", gec: "CODE ID 6.1: Fundraising Practices", bestPractice: "The Board ensures that all fundraising appeals are handled with integrity and that there is a clear contract and monitoring system for third-party fundraisers to protect donor trust." },
                    { scenario: "A viral social media post falsely accuses your {charityType} of wasting funds on 'lavish staff retreats', utilizing out-of-context photos. Angry donors are flooding your inbox threatening to pull funding, yet the internal comms team remains silent.", gec: "CODE ID 6.1: The charity actively communicates with its stakeholders to instil public confidence and maintains its public image.", bestPractice: "Proactive stakeholder communication, crisis management planning, and active public relations to defend reputational integrity." },
                    { scenario: "A major celebrity ambassador for your {charityType} is embroiled in a massive criminal scandal, and the media is demanding to know directly if the charity condones their actions.", gec: "CODE ID 6.2: Collect and respond constructively to feedback from stakeholders and the public to improve performance.", bestPractice: "Media engagement guidelines and designated, board-authorised spokespersons to effectively represent the charity." },
                    { scenario: "Your {charityType} launches an awareness campaign that is widely criticized as culturally insensitive and highly offensive to a minority group in Singapore, sparking trending outrage across local forums.", gec: "CODE ID 6.3: Implement a media communication policy to help the Board and Management build positive relationships with the media and the public.", bestPractice: "Rigorous review processes, media training, and structured media communication policies to protect reputation and build trust." }
                ]
            }
        };

